我們將是一個團射擊
松雞在黑暗中棲息。
槍聲
萊利,杏仁。
還記得降落傘嗎？
斯特林想知道
如果我們再做一次。
我不要求任何東西
除許可外。
還有60名男子。
我會根據選擇的男人
按照我自己的標準。
你為什麼要打架
在沙漠里,戴夫？
好吧,我只想殺人
他們是法西斯主義者,先生。
這個團不全是帕迪斯,
是嗎？
如果您決定加入他們,
我也會加入SAS。
他們被送到了一個地方
叫卡布裡特,
落後德國人200英里
和義大利線。
他們的生存機會有多大？
10%?
這是SAS大本營。
阻止法西斯主義的推進
整個非洲現在都落在我們身上。
上帝幫助我們。
風吹
軍樂
稍息！
付錢給瘋子。他是瘋子！
這裡！你們郵遞員有問題嗎
有一點風？
哦,帕迪,閉嘴。
我會飛其中一個
我自己操東西。
當然只是一輛卡車
雄心勃勃。
好了,這就夠了。
不應該和我一起變得聰明。
讓開。
先生們,我明白了
您對天氣的擔憂。
這不是天氣。
這是整個沙漠
升到空中。
奧金萊克將軍將搬家
他的第八軍
對抗隆美爾的前線
為了緩解托布魯克。
如果托布魯克倒下...
托布魯克不會倒下！
..接下來是開羅和蘇伊士運河。
馬爾他和地中海
像多米諾骨牌一樣倒塌。
它以隆美爾滾動結束
他的裝甲車在購物中心
朝向白金漢宮。
他的飛機不得攻擊
我們的部隊。
SAS 已經訓練了幾個月
把他們炸在地上。
我們不會退縮。
許多人的生命依賴於我們。
這是上帝的工作。
我們對此只有一次機會。
你明白嗎？你的工作是
拯救我們,回頭。
我們將走自己的路回家。
風速為30節。
15 節被認為是不安全的。
戰爭他媽的不安全！
好了,夠了。足夠。此外！
斯特林船長比你高。
你將不得不和你自己睡覺
良心如果奧金萊克的進步
被空中優勢阻止
托布魯克落入敵人之手。
讓你的人登機。
好人。
是不是太過分了？
我認為進展得相當順利。
瘋狂的混蛋。
袋子裡有家裡的信。
時間就是現在！
公司3,準備好了嗎？全體:先生！
我們啪啪啪。
是時候了,小夥子們。
公司2！
公司1！
“親愛的母親。
“如果我不回來
還有一具屍體要燃燒,
“把我的骨灰撒在石楠中
讓松雞嘲笑我的命運。
“因為現在是我和我的戰友
誰是鬆雞
飛到槍上。
“在我們之下是敵人
甚至現在都在載入
“並瞄準。”
“我最親愛的米倫。
你知道我愛你。
“我知道我可以讓你這麼開心
你不想死
“萬一天堂沒有那麼好。
“只要說是,你就會嫁給我
當我是一個合格的船長時,
“我不會問你
把它放在報紙上,
“因為我今晚可能會死。
“然後人們會說'哈哈'
或者他們會說「可憐的親愛的」,
“兩者都很可怕。
“如果這一切
是我的一個美夢,
“嗯,一直很可愛
做夢。
偉大的潛力
這些人是巨大的。
“我只是希望這些其他官員
看得出來。
」或者他們會被添加到長
銀勺餵食的白癡名單...”
“我混在一起的這套新衣服
很好奇。
「在我們短暫的時期
訓練,男人們一直活下去
“朗姆酒和酸橙,朗姆酒和茶...”
“親愛的姐姐。我有一個非常
與這個新單位一起快樂的時光。
“我真誠地希望我有機會
“向軍官展示我能做什麼
用步槍。
“這是一群優秀的小夥子,愛,
所以你不用擔心。
“你只是得到了所有的幸福
走出你可以的生活。
“任何能給你帶來幸福的東西,
孩子。
他們大喊大叫
去他媽的。
風呼嘯
“我和一位老人團聚了
阿爾斯特步槍隊的朋友。
“他是新教徒。帕迪·梅恩。
“雖然他喝得像個天主教徒。
“我們可以談論家
彼此之間。
“他就是我認識的那個人
在愛爾蘭,
“但最近,我被他改變了。”
這裡有一個人
我在阿爾斯特認識。伊恩·麥戈尼格爾。
他來自另一邊,
但我們不談論宗教。
“如果我坐起來吠叫和嚎叫
晚上,就像我有時做的那樣,
“他帶我去散步
然後扔了一根棍子給我。
“當我發現自己變成了魔鬼時,
“他提醒我,在下面
我是一個詩人。
先生！飛行員想和你說幾句話。
沒什麼可擔心的,小夥子們。
只是有點樂趣,嗯？
我們離下降還有兩分鐘。
但是斯特林船長,如果你出去
在這一點上,這將是自殺。
自殺,斯特林船長,
而已。
回頭並不丟人
在這樣的夜晚。
想想你的男人。
船上的先生們已被評估
他們的處境
並做出了決定。
繼續下降。
瘋狂的混蛋要跳了。
我們準備好了嗎,夥計們？
所有人:是的,先生！
這是十英里的步行路程
到簡易機場。
我們會轟炸他們的飛機
當他們睡覺時
並與帕迪會合
和喬克的男孩
朗姆酒早餐,是嗎？
所有人:是的！
血腥地獄,米徹姆,
你臉色蒼白。
你被誘惑了嗎？沒有,先生。不？
近！
好了,聽好了！
不許胡說八道！
站起來。
勾搭。
喊命令
行動站！
觸發釋放！
風呼嘯,男人喊
大喊大叫
喊聲
風安靜下來
遠處喊道:L支隊！
L 支隊！
霍頓？蓋茨？米查姆？
呼吸困難
L 支隊！
蓋茨,米徹姆！
呻吟
先生！
哦！先生！
呻吟
我曾經是。。。我被拖了
懸崖那邊。
啊！你能站得住嗎？
不。
我不能忍受,先生。
我聽到我的脊椎折斷了。
就像他媽的槍聲。
尖叫
你想要一些水嗎？
我受不了這種痛苦。
對不起。米徹姆,不！
喊:操！
願主憐悯
在你的靈魂上。
在我的身上。
嗯,父親？
你說戰爭可能不愉快。
我找到了炸藥和機槍。
然後財富與我們同在。
我們走。
搬到哪裡去,先生？
機場。
我們只有八個人,先生。
所以對他們來說會更難
從空中看到我們。加油。
熱。
你的胳膊怎麼了？
它壞了,先生。
然後。。。
..你很幸運,在 SAS 中,
你不必敬禮。
呐喊,嘶吼
現在,在我們繼續之前,
我們需要確定
機場在哪裡。
要做到這一點,我們需要確定
我們在哪裡。
萊利,我相信你留住了
你的指南針。
我只能肯定地說
機場在海岸上
而且我們在他們的南方。
好。
所以我們向北走。
我們只有八個人...先生。
如果你做出這樣的觀察
再。。。
..我們只有七個人。
我會向北走
即使我一個人。
右。我們還有工作要做。
你覺得呢
有一個遙遠的邊境小鎮
沙漠邊緣的某個地方
我們知道的最後一塊土地？
槍聲
有些憔悴,最終
我們的光的極限
我會發現你在等。
我們會一起去
再次攜手
進入廢墟
我們不知道
走進光明。
槍聲
啊？哦,謝謝。
麥戈尼格爾,先生。
哦。
還行。
他落地了所有的內臟...
是的,我明白。
您是否設法找到
任何武器？
只找到一挺機槍
和六枚手榴彈。
沒有炸藥或雷管。
他們都將被埋在沙子里
由於風。
我們會使用你的手榴彈。
什麼？
我們將向北走,
那他媽的方式,在那裡。
我們將到達海岸,
我們會找到我們的機場。
是的,好吧,帕迪,我們不會破壞
一個他媽的東西
用我們所擁有的,小夥子。水稻。
我們要向南走。
先生,烏雲密佈——
要下雨了。
我們需要搬到更高的地方
在我們被沖走之前。
右。
這是個搞砸的,是嗎？
這是一個偉大的老混蛋。
現在,如果我們消滅自己,
這將是唯一的事情
我們曾經做過,帕迪。
他們會說我們曾經做過的一切
被搞砸了。
GHQ會嘲笑我們。
所以你的結論
我們應該退縮嗎？
是這樣嗎？
帕迪,我不是說...
你的結論,下士,
是我們應該退縮。
我不是沒有意思。
是這樣嗎？
在他們對他做了什麼之後？
不是他們殺了他。
是風和秋天
和我們的決定,
我們都做出了決定。
對不起,先生。
帕迪,我們需要活著
再去一次。
那麼我們應該搬出去嗎？
下雨了。水稻
我們不能離開沒有你。
沒事的。去。
我會追上你的。
去。
對,收拾你的物品
然後滾蛋。
遙遠的雷聲
雨落
雷霆墜毀
來吧,庫珀,從那裡起來！
把手給我。
我們甚至知道我們要去哪裡嗎,
先生？
答案是肯定的！
千斤頂！
指南針裡有水。
也在鬆散的炸彈中。
他們渾身濕透。
完全沒用。
我們包裡的炸彈被稱為
劉易斯轟炸,因為路易斯是我的名字
我他媽的發明了它們。
我會決定它們什麼時候沒用！
喊
看在上帝的份上,把他弄出去！
來吧,你沒事吧。
除非你想讓我們都淹死,
我們必須重新開始。
你知道我曾經在泰晤士河上游泳嗎？
從塔橋。
正如尤利烏斯·凱撒
游了台伯河。
休息一下！千斤頂！
看。。。
水變成了沙漠
變成流沙。
你不能走過流沙,
更不用說游泳了。
我不是建議,萊利,
我是凱撒大帝,
但就像凱撒一樣,我的第一次嘗試
在征服被挫敗了。
愷撒撤退了,又回來了。
這就是我們將要做的。
我們會去,
但我們會回來的。
是的。
可以肯定。
來吧,你聽到了那個人的聲音。動！
風哨
我能聽到歌聲。
遙遠的歌唱
唱歌繼續
現在你唱第二節
為了讓他們放心
我們不是德國人。
在卡布裡特,我們軍官決心
沙漠程式。
如果你在夜裡看到火,
你唱第一節
和火場上的人
唱第二節。
因為如果我們是德國人,
我們不會知道這些詞。
你們中的任何一個小夥子都知道
第二節？
不。
不。井。。。
..如果你不唱
在下一個...30秒,
然後程式是開火。
如果帕迪在那裡,
這將是五秒鐘。
天啊,這一切是多麼有趣。
# 冰雹,冰雹,幫派都在這裡
# 我們到底在乎什麼？
我們到底在乎什麼？
# 冰雹,冰雹,幫派都在這裡
# 我們到底在乎什麼？
現在。。。
# 推出桶
# 我們會玩得很開心
全部:# 推出桶
加油！
# 我們有藍調在奔跑
# 唱歌、樹、塔拉瑞爾
# 唱出一首歡呼之歌
# 現在是時候滾動桶了
# 為了幫派都在這裡！#
好嗎,先生？
除了那幫人不是...
..都在這裡,是嗎？
不,這幫人並不都在這裡。
只有我們。
低沉的談話
有一些,呃...
..茶,稻田。
來吧,夥計。
我們來了。
水稻？
婉轉的音樂播放
# 部隊中的同胞
# 正在寫信
# 來自東方的某個地方
# 談論眨眼的盛宴
# 他說這隻是布萊克浦金沙
# 我們玩手榴彈
# 如果我們知道
我們會帶上
# 我們的水桶和黑桃
# 在中東
你可以玩得很開心
由地中海
# 聯手,
他們曾經說過
# 看世界
聽起來還行
# 但你整天看到的只有沙子
# 在中東
# 當你餓了
# 他們從不為你服務
一些火鍋
# 你永遠不會得到微風
吹風吹來吹去
# 頭上戴著帽子
像平底鍋蓋
# 你脫掉你的
好吧,我從來沒有做過
# 有點熱...#
看起來像我們的乘客
已經到了。
我以為有55個。
不用擔心。
您仍將獲得報酬
如果你空著開車回家。
毫米。
遠端沙漠集團！
表明自己的身份。
庫 珀。
我們是L支隊,
第一特種空勤旅。
我們剩下的。
也許這是你的態度。
也許這是你走路的方式。
但你走在鋼絲上。
這是一片大沙漠,
但是裡面沒有空間
對於現實主義者或實用主義者
或常識的信徒。
昨晚是第一個不確定的
踏上通往榮耀的漫長道路。
沒有其他敘述。
就是這樣,老男孩,來吧。
發生了什麼事？
我們經歷了一些天氣。
啊,是的。
你在這裡負責嗎？
沙漠在這裡負責。
也許你已經學會了,先生。
托布魯克有什麼消息？
我們已經遠離了廣播。
加油。洗個澡,
喝一瓶啤酒,或喝兩杯,或三杯,
然後我們將討論托布魯克。
加油。
又搞砸了？
又是一樁混蛋。
但無論如何,我們開人力車
進城。
我們還能期待多少？
啊...
..我們經歷的天氣
非常糟糕,先生。
是的。
也許不多。
右。而且,呃...
你想等多久？
哦,你知道的。
永遠。
毫米。
不,我不喜歡等待。
我在開羅有一個撲克遊戲
週四。
喊叫:我們有一些牛
四捨五入。
走吧,孩子們。加油。
在你的腳上。
加油！
音樂:慢速騎行
作者:福加特
# 慢行
# 放輕鬆
# 慢速騎行...#
# 我有很多錢
在我愛人家攢錢...#
哼唱曲調
大躍進,男孩們！
# 放輕鬆
哎 呦
# 慢行
百日咳
# 放輕鬆
# 我有心情
# 押韻是對的
嗚呼！
# 移至音樂
# 我們可以整夜滾動...#
你到底要怎麼做
在這片廣袤的土地上找到他們？
在沙漠中,一切
可以預測。
你被扔在北邊的四邊形,
12號。
然後雨來了。
不斷上漲的洪水送走你的孩子
在高地上。
鴨嘴獸嶺,
向南延伸,
所以他們向南走
直到山脊分裂。
滾回去。
哈哈！
加油！
然後他們到達綠洲,
連英國人都可以看到
由於植被。
加油！
然後他們跟隨
乾涸的河床南
直到他們到達...
..差不多...
..現在。繞到那裡。
看起來我會做的
我的撲克遊戲。
# 我有心情
# 節奏正確
# 移至音樂...#
我只數了我們八個人。
22名倖存者出...
..55.
沒有開一槍,
除了一個該死的好士兵
向他自己的大腦開火。
沒有一架飛機被摧毀,不是
一個該死的雷管引爆了。
GHQ會做什麼？
關於什麼？
什麼也沒發生。
我們的使命從未被授權,
所以沒有人會知道。
GHQ有一些人知道,
他們會笑。
但。。。
..大多數情況下,他們會太忙了
輸掉戰爭來關心。
我們將被擱置
當我們回到開羅時。
是的。
如果我們回去。
他們說男孩們
來自遠端沙漠組
可以找到鉛筆
在1000平方英里的沙漠中
只要它投下陰影。
他們可以找到被擊落的飛行員
在英格蘭大小的地區
半夜
在沙塵暴中。
所以？
所以。。。我想知道...
..如果他們能找到 SAS
一個避難所。
喇叭嗶嗶聲
你好！
百日咳
樂隊演奏爵士音樂
你在這裡幹什麼？
槍聲
我來這裏放鬆一下。
我以為是時候了
相互更新
關於最近的一些事件。
你的辦公室被鎖住了。
最近發生的事件？戴高樂將軍
需要隨時了解情況
英國戰略
在北非。
法語 75.
告訴我,什麼是將軍的
目前主要關注的問題是什麼？
操你媽。
他們在哪？
你的意思是他們在哪裡？
或者他在哪裡？
你想吃晚飯嗎？
不。告訴我他們在哪裡。
沒有人在說什麼。
對開羅來說,這是不尋常的。
清嗓子
好吧,事實是,
沒有人知道他們在哪裡。
任何倖存者都應該有
兩周前報導過。
我們沒有溝通
任何類型的。
他們怎麼了？
好吧,在你開始想像之前
一些英勇的戰鬥,
幾乎可以肯定
如果他們都死了,
他們沒有被德國人殺死
或義大利人。
他們被沙漠殺死了。
風,沙子,荊棘。
哦,通過魯莽的決定
由我們的朋友拍攝
和他的戰友
因為他們無法忍受
丟臉。
他們決定起飛
並在晚上降落傘降落
在中間
一場該死的沙塵暴。
斯特林是怎麼回事
你這麼不喜歡？
我發明瞭SAS。
他無權摧毀它
在其第一次任務中。
如果它沒有被摧毀,
它現在是一個笑柄
在少數人中
誰知道它的存在。
就百分比而言,
恐怕斯特林的機會
還活著
只是零的這一邊。
我以為你知道規則
戰時交戰。
他媽的沒事。
感覺不是。
音樂播放
那麼,現在。
我的朋友們,這是Jalo。
從字面上看,毫無疑問,
不可否認是中間的
他媽的無處可去。
如果他媽的無處可去
一個首都,就是這樣。
這將是主要街道
他媽的無處可去的城市。
市長大人會他媽的
沒有人,主持他媽的所有人
在一個沒有人的地方
周圍給他媽的。
這正是你所要求的,
斯特林船長,我說的對嗎？
我們可以繼續開車,
但我會說這個地方
與任何其他部分一樣好
我們可能無處可尋。
到德國機場有多遠？
蘇爾特位於西北350英里處。
盟軍前線？
盟軍的第一個陣地
你會來
是紐西蘭後備部隊,
80英里穿過開闊的沙漠。
但是紐西蘭人戰鬥的人
已被送往北方,
所以營地是空的。
如果您需要任何説明,
沒有。
紐西蘭營地空無一人,
你說？
幾個受傷,幾個警衛。
還有幾輛空卡車,
人們可以想像。
也許他們留下了一些槍。
也許是一些彈藥。
會有鋼琴嗎？
他媽的鋼琴？
他媽的無處可去的首都
會幫我們做得很好。
但首先,我們需要做
購物場所。
來吧,你這個害羞的混蛋。
音樂:我與法律作鬥爭
由衝突
# 在烈日下打破岩石
# 我與法律抗爭
法律贏了...#
小偷混蛋？從來不是我。
# 我與法律抗爭,法律贏了
# 我需要錢,因為我沒有錢
# 我與法律抗爭
法律贏了...#
如果我知道你要去
搶劫這個地方,
我不會帶你來的,先生。
叫我大衛,不要先生。
# ..感覺太糟糕了
# 猜猜我的比賽正在進行
# 她是最好的女孩
我曾經有過
# 我與法律抗爭,法律贏了
# 我與法律和
喇叭嘶嘶嘶
# 我與法律抗爭,法律贏了
#我与法律和...#
他們歡呼
飛利浦！哨兵值班。
在塔上,一個小時。
如果可以,也許你可以
埋葬炸藥罐
使它們遠離直接熱量。
我可以把鋼琴放在哪裡？
你彈鋼琴,帕迪？不。
Eoin試圖教我。
我想繼續。
把它放在食堂裡。
沒有食堂。
所以建立一個。
尋求？是的,老闆。
現在,昨晚
相當成功,
所以我們有一些值得慶祝的事情。
你偷了什麼
通過飲料的方式？
45加侖紐西蘭朗姆酒,先生。
好孩子。右。
所以當我們打開包裝時,
這將是雞尾酒時間。
然後當我們有了我們的
雞尾酒和太陽落山,
我認為我們應該去
有點快活。
彈藥將被登錄
弗雷澤中尉。
除非他對此有問題。
沒有,先生。
給你的車輛加油,薩德勒先生。
我們今晚去。
音樂:鋼鐵之輪
作者:撒克遜
把帳篷搭起來。
我們不要太有創意！
叫我邁克。
目標將在海岸上給出。
每人十枚路易斯炸彈。
準備就緒！
有十分鐘的保險絲
和您的30分鐘保險絲。
在可以之前不要使用炸彈
聞聞梅塞施密特的味道！
SAS任務第一！
搬出去,你們這些該死的處女。
來吧,鮑勃。
# 她有卑鄙的鋼輪
# 她有
# 鋼輪
# 談論我的鋼鐵之輪
# 鋼輪..#
我們在十英里外
蘇爾特簡易機場,正北。
我要選三個人,
把他們帶到那裡,
並盡我所能造成傷害。
劉易斯,你會帶走你的手下
到梅爾薩佈雷加。
您的目標是加油車
和供應卡車。
稻田,你帶你的手下
到塔梅特簡易機場。
您的目標是義大利卡普羅尼
戰鬥轟炸機和梅塞施密特。
比爾弗雷澤,你在哪裡？
我在這裡。加油。
我在搞砸的時候聽到
你反覆問的問題
你的指揮官。
好吧,我們已經決定,按順序
為了避免進一步的搞砸,
歡迎提問
在 SAS 中。
你會選擇四個男人
並前往阿格達比亞。
先生,如果歡迎提問,
我有一個問題。是的？
男孩們可以喝點朗姆酒嗎？
哦,當然。
請。加油。
右。我們在這裡會合
明天早上。
您和您的司機在這裡等候
為了我們的回歸。
恕我直言,先生,
我他媽的厭倦了
計程車服務。
我可以更好地閱讀這片沙漠
比這裡的任何人都要。
好吧,如果是行動
你所追求的,
和帕迪·梅恩一起去。
我們還有第二次機會。
讓我們看看星星是什麼
為我們準備了,好嗎？
男士歡呼
喊命令
它是空的。
他們都飛了。
狗屎。
主保險絲。十分鐘。
去。
萊利。以一個人為例,
向右走。
杏仁,拿三個人,
從後方側翼回合。
八分鐘后回到這裡。
盡可能多地撞卡車。
看在上帝的份上,不要被人看到。
去。
薩德勒。哼？
這是一枚著名的路易斯炸彈。
從未聽說過。
那是因為它只有名聲
在我們中間。
喬克·路易斯發明瞭它。
他給我們煮了一個原型。
今晚,我們要
試試看。
您以前從未使用過它們？
不,但喬克·路易斯非常聰明。
我相信我們會沒事的。
這些都已準備就緒
十分鐘后就走了,對吧？
從現在開始？
從現在開始。
所以我們應該他媽的
加油,帕迪。
十分鐘足夠了,男孩們。
有足夠的時間做什麼？
遙遠的笑聲和喋喋不休
他們喝醉了,帕迪。
我們可以炸毀炸彈
並在他們知道之前消失...
唾手可得的果實,成熟的蘋果。
那些醉漢是飛行員
和工程師清醒時。
所以他媽的按照慣例,
日內瓦或其他。
這是我們他媽的工作,男孩們。
這就是我們,
殺戮和被殺。
任何男人都太公正、善良和高尚
因為這樣的工作可以留下來,
擦亮他們的子彈,
做一條漂亮的小項鍊。
我自己,我很平靜。
我從不參加派對
無論如何,我都被邀請參加。
低聲說:走。
那個,那個,那個。
喋喋不休
喧鬧的談話,錄音播放
你想要一盞燈嗎？
給你。
不。英語,實際上。
笑
英語！
是的。
英語。
你好！
扼流圈
刀刮擦
喇叭布拉雷斯
用德語喊叫
他媽的。
晚上好。
錄音播放
炮火
搖滾樂
找掩護！
喊
三分鐘,炸彈爆炸！
包括這輛卡車！
不理想。
嗚咽
他們現在已經受夠了,帕迪。
水稻！
炮火
兩分鐘吹飛機,
男孩。移動！
他媽的招式！
千斤頂？
一分鐘后,這輛卡車即將駛來
有點熱！
沒有説明。
加油！移動！
喊
帕迪在哪裡？
他到底在哪裡？
口哨
水稻！
去！
尖叫
炸彈！
喊
移動！
去！去！
水稻！
他們嘩啦啦
回到那些吉普車上。
稻田,快點！
水稻！
音樂:新玫瑰
作者:《詛咒》
笑
# 我內心有一種感覺
爆炸淹沒音樂
# 我猜這些東西
必須
# 我有一朵新玫瑰
我有很好的
# 猜猜我知道我總是會
# 我不能停下來胡鬧
哎 呦
# 我在城裡得到了一朵嶄新的玫瑰
# 見太陽
看到太陽,它閃耀
# 我猜這些東西
必須
# 我得到了一朵新玫瑰
我做得很好...#
遠處的爆炸
男孩。
他們笑了
那是梅爾薩佈雷加和阿格達比亞
被吹到地獄了,先生。
是的！
遠處的爆炸
這就是Tamet的Paddy Mayne。
笑
我在黑暗中
和蘇爾特的沉默。
這不是比賽,先生。
當然是他媽的。
加油。
摩爾斯電碼
先生。 來自情報部門的報告。
摩爾斯電碼繼續
啊,親愛的。
終於,我有事要彙報了
這確實是真的。
其實他媽的沒錯。
截獲的無線電通信
德國人之間
和義大利空軍司令部
說前天晚上,
48架戰鬥轟炸機
戰鬥機被摧毀
在地面上時
在兩個獨立的空軍基地——
被出現的男人摧毀
顯然不知從何而來
然後消失在沙漠中。
此外,還有17輛油罐車,
補給卡車、彈藥箱
炸藥被銷毀
在梅爾薩佈雷加。
顯然,那些抓住的少數人
攻擊者一瞥
說他們沒有穿制服
看起來像野蠻人。
所以他還活著。
重要的事情
是我的創造是活的。
我認為發生了什麼的奧秘
到L支隊第一SAS旅
可能已經解決了,先生。
嗯,我覺得那個男孩
可能只是贏了他的賭注。
鋼琴彈奏簡單的曲調
尾巴掉落
重新啟動
哦,我明白。
明白了。
音樂:粉碎它
作者:《詛咒》
讓遊戲開始吧。
# 我們現在一直在哭
太久了
# 現在我們要跳舞了
到另一首歌
# 我要尖叫和大喊大叫
直到我垂死的呼吸
# 我要把它砸碎
直到一無所有
#哦,砸碎它！
# 砸碎它,砸碎它！
# 人們叫我反派
哦,太可惜了
# 也許是我的衣服
一定是罪魁禍首
# 我什至不在乎我是否看起來一團糟
# 不想當傻瓜
像其他人一樣
# 哦,砸碎它
# 砸碎它,砸碎它！#
We would be a regiment shooting
grouse in their roost in the dark.
GUNSHOT
Riley, Almonds.
Remember the parachutes?
Stirling wants to know
if we'll do it again.
I'm not asking for anything
other than permission.
And 60 men.
Men I will choose according
to my own criteria.
Why do you want to fight
in the desert, Dave?
Well, I just want to kill
them fascists, sir.
This regiment isn't all Paddies,
is it?
If you decide to join them,
I will join the SAS too.
They've been sent to a place
called Kabrit,
200 miles behind the German
and Italian lines.
What are their chances of survival?
10%?
This is SAS base camp.
Stopping the advance of fascism
across Africa is now down to us.
God help us.
WIND BLOWS
MILITARY MUSIC
At ease!
Pay the madman. He is the madman!
Here! Do you postmen have a problem
with a wee bit of wind?
Oh, Paddy, shut up.
I'd fly one of these
fuckin' things myself.
Sure it's just a truck
with a lot of ambition.
OK, that's enough.
Shouldn't get fucking smart with me.
Step aside.
Gentlemen, I understand
your concerns regarding the weather.
This isn't weather.
This is the whole desert
risen up into the air.
General Auchinleck will move
his eighth army
against Rommel's front line
in order to relieve Tobruk.
If Tobruk falls...
Tobruk will not fall!
..Cairo and the Suez Canal are next.
Malta and the Mediterranean
topple like dominoes.
It ends with Rommel rolling
his Panzers up the Mall
towards Buckingham Palace.
His planes must not attack
our troops.
The SAS have trained for months
to blow them up on the ground.
We will not be stood down.
Many lives depend on us.
It's God's work.
We have one shot at this.
Do you understand? Your job is to
deliver us and turn back.
We will make our own way home.
The wind is 30 knots.
15 knots is considered unsafe.
War is fucking unsafe!
OK, enough. Enough. Besides!
Captain Stirling outranks you.
You will have to sleep with your own
conscience if Auchinleck's advance
is stopped by air superiority
and Tobruk falls to the enemy.
Get your men boarded.
Good man.
Was that too much?
I think it went rather well.
Mad bastard.
Letters from home in the bag.
Time is now!
Corp 3, ready? ALL: Sir!
Off we pop.
It's time, lads.
Corp 2!
Corp 1!
"Dear Mother.
"If I don't return
and there is a body to burn,
"spread my ashes among the heather
and let the grouse laugh at my fate.
"Because now it is I and my comrades
"who are the grouse
flying onto the gun.
"And below us the enemy
are even now loading up
"and taking aim."
"My dearest Mirren.
You know I love you.
"I know I could make you so happy
that you wouldn't want to die
"in case heaven wasn't as good.
"Just say yes, you'll marry me
when I'm a proper captain,
"and I won't ask you
to put it in the papers,
"because I might die tonight.
"And then people would say 'ha-ha'
or they would say 'poor dear',
"and both are horrid.
"And if all this
is a lovely dream of mine,
"well, it has been lovely
dreaming it."
"The potential for greatness
of these men is huge.
"I just hope these other officers
can see that.
"Or they'll be added to the long
list of silver-spoon-fed idiots..."
"This new outfit I got mixed up in
is pretty curious.
"During our brief period of
training, the men have lived on
"rum and lime, rum and tea..."
"Dear sister. I'm having a very
jolly time with this new unit.
"I sincerely hope I get a chance
"to show the officers what I can do
with a rifle."
"It's a fine crowd of lads, love,
so you're not to worry.
"You just get all the happiness
out of life that you can.
"Anything that brings you happiness,
kid."
THEY SHOUT
Fuck this.
WIND HOWLS
"I have been reunited with an old
friend from the Ulster Rifles.
"He's a Protestant. Paddy Mayne.
"Though he drinks like a Catholic."
"We're able to talk about home
to each other.
"He's the same man I knew
in Ireland,
"but lately, I'm changed by him."
"There's a fellow here
I knew in Ulster. Eoin McGonigal.
"He's from the other side,
but we don't talk religion.
"If I sit up barking and howling
at night, as I sometimes do,
"he takes me for a walk
and throws a stick for me.
"When I find myself become a devil,
"he reminds me that underneath
I am a poet."
Sir! Pilot wants a word with you.
Nothing to worry about, lads.
Just a bit of fun, eh?
We're two minutes from the drop.
But Captain Stirling, if you go out
in this, it will be suicide.
Suicide, Captain Stirling,
nothing more.
There's no shame in turning back
on a night like this.
Think of your men.
Gentlemen aboard have been appraised
of their circumstances
and have made their decisions.
Proceed with your descent.
The mad bastards are going to jump.
Are we ready, chaps?
ALL: Yes, sir!
It's a ten-mile stroll
to the airstrips.
We'll bomb their planes
while they sleep
and rendezvous with Paddy
and Jock's boys
for a rum breakfast, yes?
ALL: Yes!
Bloody hell, Mitcham,
you're looking pale.
Are you tempted? No, sir. No?
Nah!
All right, listen up!
No dicking about!
Stand up.
Hook up.
SHOUTS ORDERS
Action stations!
Trigger release!
WIND HOWLS, MAN SHOUTS
YELLING
SHOUTS
WIND QUIETENS
DISTANT SHOUTING: L Detachment!
L Detachment!
Holden? Gates? Mitcham?
RAGGED BREATHING
L Detachment!
Gates, Mitcham!
GROANS
Sir!
Oh! Sir!
GROANS
I was... I was dragged
over the cliff.
Aaah! Can you stand?
No.
I cannot stand, sir.
I heard my spine snap.
Like a fucking gunshot.
SCREAMS
Do you want some water?
I cannot stand this pain.
I'm sorry. Mitcham, no!
SHOUTS: Fuck!
May the Lord have mercy
on your soul.
And on mine.
Well, Father?
You said war could be unpleasant.
I found explosives and machine guns.
Then fortune is with us.
Let's move.
Move where, sir?
The airfields.
There are only eight of us, sir.
So it'll be harder for them
to see us from the air. Come on.
Warm up.
What's wrong with your arm?
It's broken, sir.
Then...
..you are lucky, in the SAS,
you don't have to salute.
SHOUTS, GRUNTS
Now, before we proceed,
we need to ascertain
where the airfields are.
And to do that, we need to ascertain
where we are.
Riley, I believe you retained
your compass.
All I can say for sure is
that the airfields are on the coast
and that we are south of them.
Good.
So we head north.
There are only eight of us...sir.
If you make that observation
again...
..there will only be seven of us.
I would head north
even if I were alone.
Right. We've got work to do.
Do you think
there's a far border town
Somewhere at the desert's edge
The last of the lands we know?
GUNSHOT
Some gaunt, eventual
limit of our light
In which I'll find you waiting.
And we'll go together
hand in hand again
Out there into the wastes
we know not
Into the light.
GUNSHOT
Eh? Oh, thanks.
McGonigal, sir.
Oh.
OK.
He landed all gut...
Yes, I understand.
Did you manage to locate
any of the weapons?
Found only one machine gun
and six grenades.
No explosives or detonators.
They will all be buried in the sand
on account of the wind.
We'll use your grenades.
You what?
We will head north,
that fucking way, up there.
And we will reach the coast,
and we will find our airfields.
Yeah, well, Paddy, we won't destroy
a single fucking thing
with what we've got, lad. Paddy.
We were going to head south.
Sir, there were dark clouds -
it's going to rain.
We need to move to a higher ground
before we get washed away.
Right.
This was a fuck-up, yeah?
And a grand old fuck-up it was.
Now, if we wipe ourselves out,
it will be the only thing
that we ever did, Paddy.
They'll say that all we ever did
was fuck up.
GHQ will laugh at us.
So your conclusion
is that we should stand down?
Is that it?
Paddy, I didn't mean...
Your conclusion, Corporal,
is that we should stand down.
I don't mean nothing by it.
Is that it?
After what they've done to him?
It wasn't them that killed him.
It was the wind and the fall
and our decision,
the decision we all made.
Sorry, sir.
Paddy, we need to be alive
to go again.
So should we move out?
It's rain. Paddy,
we can't leave without you.
It's fine. Go.
I'll catch you up.
Go.
Right, gather your belongings
and fuck off.
DISTANT THUNDER
RAIN FALLS
THUNDER CRASHES
Come on, Cooper, get up from there!
Give me your hand.
Do we even know where we're going,
sir?
Of course!
Jack!
There's water in the compass.
Also in the loose bombs.
They're drenched.
Completely useless.
The bombs in our packs are called
Lewes bombs because Lewes is my name
and I fucking invented them.
I will decide when they are useless!
SHOUTING
Get him out, for God's sake!
Come on, you're all right.
Unless you want us all to drown,
we must start back.
Do you know I once swam the Thames?
From Tower Bridge.
Just as Julius Caesar
swam the Tiber.
Rest a bit! Jack!
Look...
the water's turned the desert
into quicksand.
You can't walk across quicksand,
let alone swim it.
I am not suggesting, Riley,
that I am Julius Caesar,
but like Caesar, my first attempt
at conquest has been thwarted.
Caesar withdrew and came back.
That is what we will do.
We will go,
but we will come back.
Yes.
With certainty.
Come on, you heard the man. Move!
WIND WHISTLES
I can hear singing.
DISTANT SINGING
SINGING CONTINUES
Now you sing the second verse
in order to reassure them
that we are not German.
In Kabrit, we officers resolved
a desert procedure.
If you see a fire in the night,
you sing the first verse
and the people at the fire
sing the second verse.
Because if we were Germans,
we wouldn't know the words.
Any of you lads know
the second verse?
No.
No. Well...
..if you don't sing it
in the next...30 seconds,
then the procedure is to open fire.
If Paddy's out there,
it'll be five seconds.
God, how amusing this all is.
# Hail, hail, the gang's all here
# What the hell do we care?
What the hell do we care?
# Hail, hail, the gang's all here
# What the hell do we care?
Now...
# Roll out the barrel
# We'll have a barrel of fun
ALL: # Roll out the barrel
Come on!
# We've got the blues on the run
# Zing, boom, tararrel
# Sing out a song of good cheer
# Now it's time to roll the barrel
# For the gang's all here! #
All right, sir?
Except the gang is not...
..all here, is it?
No, the gang is not all here.
Just us.
MUFFLED CONVERSATION
There's some, er...
..tea, Paddy.
Come on, mate.
There we are.
Paddy?
JAUNTY MUSIC PLAYING
# A fellow in the forces
# Was writing a letter
# From somewhere in the east
# Talk of a blinking feast
# He says it's just Blackpool Sands
# We play with hands grenades
# If we had known
we would have brought along
# Our buckets and spades
# Out in the Middle East
You can have a lot of fun
by the Mediterranean
# Join the forces,
they used to say
# And see the world
It sounds OK
# But you see nowt but sand all day
# Out in the Middle East
# And when you're hungry
# They never serve you up
some hot pot
# You never get a gentle breeze
a-blowing wind round your whatnot
# On your heads you've hats
like saucepan lids
# You take off your
well-I-never-dids
# It gets a bit hot... #
Looks like our passengers
have arrived.
I thought there were 55 of them.
Don't worry.
You'll still be paid
if you drive home empty.
Mm.
Long Range Desert Group!
Identify yourself.
Cooper.
We are L Detachment,
First Special Air Service Brigade.
What's left of us.
Maybe it's your attitude.
Maybe it's the way you walk.
But you are walking on a tightrope.
This is a big desert,
but there is no room in it
for realists or pragmatists
or believers in common sense.
Last night was the first uncertain
step on the long walk to glory.
There is no other narrative.
That's it, old boy, come on.
What happened?
We experienced some weather.
Ah, yes.
Are you in charge here?
The desert's in charge here.
Maybe you've learned that, sir.
What news of Tobruk?
We've been away from radio.
Come on. Get a nice bath,
drink a beer, or two, or three,
and then we'll talk about Tobruk.
Come on.
Another fuck-up?
Another fuck-up.
But anyway, we run the rickshaws
into town.
How many more can we expect?
Ah, well...
..the weather we experienced
was very bad, sir.
Yes.
Perhaps not many.
Right. And, er...
how long do you want to wait?
Oh, you know.
Forever.
Mm.
No. I don't like waiting around.
I have a poker game in Cairo
on Thursdays.
SHOUTS: We have some cattle
to round up.
Let's go, boys. Come on.
On your feet.
Come on!
MUSIC: Slow Ride
by Foghat
# Slow ride
# Take it easy
# Slow ride... #
# I've got a great big amount
saved up in my lover's house... #
HUMS TUNE
Big leap, boys!
# Take it easy
WHOOPS
# Slow ride
WHOOPING
# Take it easy
# I'm in the mood
# The rhymes is right
Woohoo!
# Move to the music
# We can roll all night... #
How the hell are you going to
find them in this vastness?
In the desert, everything
can be predicted.
You were dropped in the north quad,
number 12.
Then rain came.
Rising flood sends your boys
on to high ground.
The Platypus Ridge,
which runs south,
so they walk south
until the ridge splits.
Fuck off back there.
Ha-ha!
Come on!
Then they reach the oasis,
which even the Brits can see
on account of the vegetation.
Come on!
Then they follow
the dried-up riverbed south
until they arrive...
..right just about...
..now. Round about there.
Looks like I will make
my poker game.
# I'm in the mood
# The rhythm is right
# Move to the music... #
I only count eight of our men.
22 survivors out of...
..55.
Not a shot fired,
except a damn good soldier
firing into his own brain.
Not a plane destroyed, not
a fucking detonator detonated.
What will GHQ do?
About what?
Nothing happened.
Our mission was never authorised,
so no-one will know.
There are a few at GHQ that do know,
and they will laugh.
But...
..mostly they will be too busy
losing the war to care.
And we will be stood down
when we get back to Cairo.
Yes.
If we go back.
They say the boys
from the Long Range Desert Group
can find a pencil
in 1,000 square miles of desert
just so long as it casts a shadow.
They can find a downed pilot
in an area the size of England
in the middle of the night
in a sandstorm.
So?
So...I wonder...
..if they can find the SAS
a place of sanctuary.
HORN BEEPS
Hello!
WHOOPING
BAND PLAYS JAZZ MUSIC
What are you doing here?
GUNSHOT
I come here to relax.
I thought it was time for us
to update each other
on some recent events.
Your office was locked.
Recent events? General de Gaulle
needs to be kept informed
of British strategies
in North Africa.
French 75.
Tell me, what is the general's
main concern at the moment?
Fuck you.
Where are they?
Do you mean where are they?
Or where is he?
Do you want to have dinner?
No. Just tell me where they are.
No-one is saying anything.
For Cairo, that is unusual.
CLEARS THROAT
Well, truth is,
no-one knows where they are.
Any survivors should have
reported back two weeks ago.
We've had no communications
of any sort.
What happened to them?
Well, before you begin to imagine
some heroic combat,
it's almost certain
that if they are all dead,
they weren't killed by the Germans
or the Italians.
They were killed by the desert.
The wind, the sand, the thorns.
Oh, and by the reckless decision
taken by our friend
and his comrades
because they couldn't stand
to lose face.
They decided to take off
and make a parachute drop at night
in the middle of
a fucking sandstorm.
What is it about Stirling
that you dislike so much?
I invented the SAS.
And he had no right to destroy it
on its first mission.
And if it's not destroyed,
it's now a laughing stock
among the few people
who even know it exists.
In terms of percentage,
I'm afraid the chances of Stirling
being still alive
are just this side of zero.
I thought you knew the rules
of engagement in time of war.
Fucking is fine.
Feeling is not.
MUSIC PLAYING
Now, then.
This, my friends, is Jalo.
Literally, unquestionably,
undeniably the middle
of fucking nowhere.
If fucking nowhere had
a capital city, this would be it.
And this would be the main street
of fucking nowhere city.
And the Lord Mayor would be fucking
no-one, presiding over fuck all
in a place where there was no-one
around to give a fuck.
Which is exactly what you asked for,
Captain Stirling, am I right?
We could carry on driving,
but I'd say this place
is as good as any other part
of nowhere we might find.
How far to the German airfield?
Sirte is 350 miles north-west.
The Allied front line?
The first Allied position
you'd come to
is the New Zealand Reserve troop,
80 miles across open desert.
But the Kiwi fighting men
have been sent north,
so the camp is empty.
If you need any help,
there isn't any.
The New Zealand camp is empty,
you say?
A few wounded, a few guards.
And a few empty trucks,
one might imagine.
Maybe some guns they left behind.
Maybe some ammunition.
Will there be a piano?
A fucking piano?
The capital city of fucking nowhere
will do us just fine.
But first, we need to do
a spot of shopping.
Come on, you dishy bastard.
MUSIC: I Fought The Law
by The Clash
# Breakin' rocks in the hot sun
# I fought the law
and the law won... #
Thieving bastard? Never me.
# I fought the law and the law won
# I needed money cos I had none
# I fought the law
and the law won... #
If I'd known you were going
to rob the place,
I wouldn't have brought you, sir.
Call me David, not sir.
# ..and it feels so bad
# Guess my race is run
# She's the best girl
that I ever had
# I fought the law and the law won
# I fought the law and the
HORNS BLARE
# I fought the law and the law won
# I fought the law and the... #
THEY CHEER
Philips! Sentry duty.
On the tower, one hour.
And if you can, perhaps you might
bury the explosive canisters
to keep them out of the direct heat.
Where can I put the piano?
You play the piano, Paddy? No.
Eoin was trying to teach me.
I want to carry on.
Put it in the mess hall.
There isn't a mess hall.
So build one.
Seekings? Yes, boss.
Now, last night
was rather a success,
so we have something to celebrate.
What did you steal
by way of drinks?
45 gallons of New Zealand rum, sir.
Good boy. Right.
So by the time that we're unpacked,
it will be cocktail hour.
And then when we've had our
cocktails and the sun is set,
I think we should go for
a bit of jolly.
Ammunition will be signed in
by Lieutenant Fraser.
Unless he has a problem with that.
No, sir.
Refuel your vehicles, Mr Sadler.
We go tonight.
MUSIC: Wheels of Steel
by Saxon
Get the tents up.
Let's not be too creative!
Call me Mike.
Targets will be given on the coast.
Ten Lewes bombs to each man.
At the ready!
Have your ten-minute fuses
and your 30-minute fuses.
Do not use your bombs until you can
smell the Messerschmitts!
SAS mission number one!
Move out, you fucking virgins.
Come on, Bob.
# She's got mean wheels of steel
# She's got
# Wheels of steel
# Talkin' about my wheels of steel
# Wheels of steel.. #
We are ten miles outside of
Sirte airstrip, directly north.
I'm going to pick three men,
take them there,
and do what damage I can.
Lewes, you will take your men
to Mersa Brega.
Your target is fuel trucks
and supply trucks.
Paddy, you will take your men
to Tamet Airstrip.
Your target is Italian Caproni
fighter bombers and Messerschmitts.
Bill Fraser, where are you?
I'm here. Come on.
I hear during the fuck-up
that you repeatedly asked questions
of your commanding officer.
Well, we have decided, in order
to avoid further fuck-ups,
that questions are to be welcomed
in the SAS.
You will pick four men
and travel to Agedabia.
If questions are welcome, sir,
I've got a question. Yes?
Can me the boys have some rum?
Oh, absolutely.
Please. Come on.
Right. We rendezvous back here
tomorrow morning.
You and your drivers wait here
for our return.
With all due respect, sir,
I'm fucking sick of being
the taxi service.
I can read this desert better
than any man here.
Well, if it's action
that you're after,
go with Paddy Mayne.
We have a second chance.
Let's see what the stars
have in store for us, shall we?
MEN CHEER
SHOUTS ORDERS
It's empty.
They've all flown.
Shit.
Prime fuses. Ten minutes.
Go.
Riley. Take one man,
go to the right.
Almonds, take three men,
flank round from the rear.
Back here in eight minutes.
Hit as many trucks as you can.
For God's sake, don't be seen.
Go.
Sadler. Huh?
This is a famous Lewes bomb.
Never heard of it.
That's because it's only famous
amongst us.
Jock Lewes invented it.
He cooked us up a prototype.
Tonight, we're going to
try them out.
You've never used them before?
No, but Jock Lewes is very smart.
I'm sure we'll be fine.
These are all being primed and ready
to go off in ten minutes, right?
From now?
From now.
So we should fucking
get on with it, Paddy.
Ten minutes is plenty of time, boys.
Plenty of time for what?
DISTANT LAUGHTER AND CHATTER
They're drunk, Paddy.
We could blow the bombs
and be gone before they know...
Low-hanging fruit, ripe apples.
Those drunks are pilots
and engineers when they sober up.
So to fuck with conventions,
Geneva or otherwise.
This is our fucking work, boys.
This is who we are,
to kill and be killed.
Any man too just and good and noble
for work like this can stay behind,
polish their bullets,
make a nice wee necklace.
Myself, I am tranquil.
I never go to parties
to which I am invited anyway.
WHISPERS: Go.
Go, go, go.
CHATTER
RAUCOUS CONVERSATION, RECORD PLAYS
Would you like a light?
Here you are.
No. English, actually.
LAUGHS
Inglese!
Si.
English.
Hello!
CHOKES
KNIFE SCRAPES
HORN BLARES
SHOUTS IN GERMAN
Fuck.
Good evening.
RECORD PLAYING
GUNFIRE
ROCK MUSIC
Take cover!
SHOUTING
Three minutes, the bombs go off!
Including this truck!
Not ideal.
WHIMPERING
They've had enough now, Paddy.
Paddy!
GUNFIRE
Two minutes to blow the planes,
boys. Move!
Fucking move!
Jack?
In one minute, this truck's about to
get a bit hot!
Not helpful.
Come on! Move!
SHOUTING
Where's Paddy?
Where on earth is he?
WHISTLES
Paddy!
Go!
SCREAMING
The bombs!
SHOUTING
Move!
Go! Go!
Paddy!
THEY WHOOP
Get back to those Jeeps.
Paddy, hurry up!
Paddy!
MUSIC: New Rose
by The Damned
LAUGHS
# I've got a feeling inside me
EXPLOSIONS DROWN MUSIC
# I guess these things
have got to be
# I've got a new rose
I've got it good
# Guess I knew that I always would
# I can't stop to mess around
WHOOPS
# I got a brand-new rose in town
# See the sun
See the sun, it shines
# I guess these things
have got to be
# I got a new rose
I got it good... #
DISTANT EXPLOSIONS
Boys.
THEY LAUGH
That's Mersa Brega and Agedabia
blown to hell, sir.
Yes!
DISTANT EXPLOSIONS
And that's Paddy Mayne at Tamet.
LAUGHS
And here am I in the dark
and silence in Sirte.
It's not a competition, sir.
Of course it fucking is.
Come on.
MORSE CODE
Sir. Report from intelligence.
MORSE CODE CONTINUES
Ah, my dear.
At last, I have something to report
that's actually true.
Actually fucking true.
Intercepted radio communications
between the German
and Italian Air Force commands
says that the night before last,
48 fighter bombers
and fighter aircraft were destroyed
while on the ground
at two separate air bases -
destroyed by men who appeared
apparently from nowhere
and disappeared into the desert.
Also, 17 fuel tankers,
supply trucks, ammunition crates
and explosives were destroyed
at Mersa Brega.
Apparently, those few who caught
a glimpse of the attackers
said they wore no uniforms
and looked like wild savages.
So he's alive.
The important thing
is that my creation is alive.
I think the mystery of what happened
to L Detachment First SAS Brigade
may have been solved, sir.
Well, I think that boy
might just have won his bet.
PIANO PLAYS SIMPLE TUNE
TAILS OFF
RESTARTS
Oh, I see.
I see.
MUSIC: Smash It Up
by The Damned
Let the games begin.
# We've been crying now
for much too long
# And now we're gonna dance
to a different song
# I'm gonna scream and shout
till my dying breath
# I'm gonna smash it up
till there's nothing left
# Ooh, smash it up!
# Smash it up, smash it up!
# People call me villain
Oh, it's such a shame
# Maybe its my clothes
must be to blame
# I don't even care if I look a mess
# Don't want to be a sucker
like all the rest
# Ooh, smash it up
# Smash it up, smash it up! #